You are now listening to 103.5
FM.
You've been in the dark for
way too long.
It's time to walk into the
light and accept your fate
with open arms.
Scared?
Don't worry.
We'll be there to hold your
hand and guide you through
this painless transition.
But what's the rush?
Just relax and enjoy another
hour of commercial free music
on 103.5 Don FM.
Stay tuned.
I was born
in a city
where the winter nights don't
ever sleep.
So there's life
always with me.
The ice and suck my face will
never be
love.
Love.
Every time
you try to fix me.
I know you'll never find that
missing piece.
When you cry
cause you miss me.
All I ever told you that I'll
never leave.
But I sacrifice
your love for more than all.
I tried to put up.
But I can't
lay me down.
I don't understand.
For your
love I try.
I don't wanna say
goodbyes.
But I love
my time.
Love.
I hold you through the
toughest parts.
When you feel like it's the
end.
Cause life is still worth
living.
It is.
Life is still worth living.
I can breathe,
you can pick you up and fuck
like your friends.
But don't be catching feelings.
Don't be out of it.
Get your feelings.
Cause I sacrifice
your love for
the night
I tried to put up a fight.
Can't toy me down.
I don't want to sound
like I
don't wanna love.
I tried
I don't wanna say
goodbyes.
But I love
my time.
I don't wanna say
Help us if we're gonna
know what
I tried.
I don't wanna say.
But I've got the
right to
know.
I'll keep up.
I hope you know that.
Hey,
I tried.
Oh,
baby,
I hope you know I love
my time.
Oh,
I don't wanna.
I wanna
die.
I don't wanna
be terrified.
But I love my time.
I.
Love.